I'm in Korea.
Okay, I want to try the shrimp one
first.
It's good.
>> [music]
>> Oh my god.
Hello, it's trying to escape. OH, IT'S A
WOW, AGAIN AND AGAIN AND AGAIN.
OH MY GOSH. WOW.
Hi look at that. Hey, welcome or welcome
back to my [music] YouTube channel. And
for today's video, I'm in Korea.
I don't post real time anymore [music]
cuz so Yes, I'm here to heal.
No, I'm here in Korea because
So, I really need to go somewhere.
This is the best [music] time, you know,
to travel. I'm with my uncle, guys.
And for
We're going to food trip tayo and I
booked a food tour. My uncle was like
Para I'm motivated to come home again
because Guys, come back home again and
come back home again. I'm a traveler
like this
video
and I like to Uber before my healing
like my commute, but now I prefer to go
to Uber. So, we are going there. And you
know [music] what? Whenever I travel,
cuz you got to my travel there. Law of
manifestation and then see you go. We
are entering a tunnel with the new line.
We're going to light. Again, we're going
to light, guys.
I'm a mad traveler. Whenever I go, you
have to come back again. So, you want to
come back again and again and again, but
That's okay cuz it's for me
manifestation cuz you know I okay that I
wasn't able to go to this place cuz I
sure hope not. I'll be back [music]
in place cuz yeah I don't care then I
got to be a always better than I could
have put [music] in the country. May not
have been a mug one last 2024
and I'm like okay I didn't go to the gas
station cuz I'll be back and now [music]
I'm here. Just a tip to my followers
but I love the law of manifestation so
yeah. I'll see you guys before we put
the camera [music] and I decided to go
into because I like to see you guys
enjoy it when I eat so yeah. Let's go.
>> [music]
>> I'm going to get that is so we're here
now. It's [music] a food market barrel.
I booked a tour now so marong meeting
place. I'm just not sure where and you
did it
you know what I'm going to call long
sleeve shirt.
I tell you it's warm though I'm going to
make a couple of long sleeve shirts.
I got jacket so you know I got to make a
couple of Tito's but you know guys after
my pregnancy I'm not that long again
anymore. So I didn't have friend cuz I'm
going to die cuz I am going to die
>> [laughter]
>> cuz I am going to look for the meeting
place. We're just going to walk around.
>> [music]
>> Guys I lied it's cold. So I am going to
go to the gay bar and have fun.
>> [music]
>> Guys look at the camera strawberry. This
is Korean strawberry it's only 200
pesos. We're going to buy later. Okay so
we're here at the meeting spot. Guys I'm
going to leave cuz I am going to book
okay and your tour guide now
cutie shot.
I bought now and I'm going to get
better.
>> Last time it always
by the way, once again, there is Is this
your first time in Korea? I'm not style.
Which is one of the most popular Korean
song.
So, I think to get to know each other
we're better with this song next.
>> I'm Bea from New York Cobao.
Hi, I'm Bea. I'm from the Philippines.
My favorite Korean dish is samgyeopsal.
>> [laughter]
>> Yes.
>> Call me Jones. I'm also from the
Philippines and no allergies. My
favorite food is also fried chicken.
>> Dora, Dora, Dora [music] the Explorer.
>> Have you heard of kimbap?
>> Yes.
>> Have you tried it before?
I see.
Kim means seaweed. Bap means cooked
rice. So, it's literally seaweed rice
roll. And you can think of it like a
Korean style food.
>> [music]
>> Guys, nakakainis kasi
Guys, I wasn't able to video it, the
kimbap.
>> Thank you.
>> It's not an octopus. It's a rice cake.
Yes. It's so thick in our version.
>> Authentic. [music]
A little bit too much sugar.
It's spicy.
I really like that.
>> Is this spice level okay for you?
>> Yes.
>> Is it okay?
If it's a little spicy, then our next
plate will have a lot of water, so don't
worry. We have water.
>> [music]
>> Authentic. I mean, we're in Korea, so I
guess.
Going to heaven.
>> [music]
>> The vendors the vendors that I mentioned
before you can see the picture of the
restaurant.
>> Korean pancake.
>> [music]
>> Guys, so there's two pancakes. Yellow
and brown.
Has pork and then the yellow one.
But I don't know the difference in the
yellow.
>> It's like nutty flavor with
yellow bean.
>> Okay.
>> [laughter]
[music]
>> Do you want me to pour for you?
>> Oh, no. Okay.
Okay, thank you.
What's thinking Korean food something?
There's some spicy
Well, alcoholic.
We I recommend this tour food guy.
No, actually if you need a food but my
god like my history guy
fun fact about myself is I actually love
history. It's nice to learn some
information. Oh, thank you.
I'm going to get sauce.
>> Now, there's Togi.
>> [music]
>> Good first meal.
Guys, you know what? Before I don't eat
on
when I was young.
>> Yeah.
>> She in Korea.
Which one do you prefer?
The yellow one.
I prefer the brown one.
Paris, people watching. Dito na man.
Hindi na man
Korea for so many times, but this is the
first time. This is the first time you
went to a market like this.
>> Are those like exotic?
Are those exotic or no?
>> Oh my god. I'm not going to eat that,
bro.
>> Are those worms?
>> I'm not going to eat that.
>> A lot of different types of side dish.
>> Side dish, side dish.
>> Koreans also make fish and rice
literally every day. Mixed with a lot of
different types of fish.
>> [music]
>> So, they taste raw octopus.
It's not that spicy, but it tastes
strong in both flavors.
>> Strong octopus.
>> I'll try. Yeah, [laughter] how many
>> Okay, update me na lang. Ayoko na.
>> You're not going to try?
>> No.
>> No, you try.
>> We don't have a boat.
>> [laughter]
>> Guys, I'm sorry. I can't.
>> Raw octopus, my first time.
>> Really?
>> This is my first time.
>> You know, it's okay.
It's like the the one that you like, the
fish cake, I don't know.
>> How is it? Is it okay?
And our second side is that we're going
to try
baby stir-fried crab. It was fried and
then stir-fried once again
It has four different flavors. That
means you can eat the whole thing. Yeah,
including the shell.
>> Okay, I'm going to try that.
>> Including the shell.
>> It's really hard to eat.
>> It's actually good.
Pickled garlic. One of the largest
consumers of garlic in the world because
on average one Korean person eats 7 to 8
kg of garlic in a year. But we usually
enjoy garlic after try some oily food
like fried foods or Korean barbecue
cleans the palate. But this one is
pickled, right? So you can also match
with the rice.
>> Okay, we're going to try pickled garlic.
>> Is this pickled? Yeah, pickled garlic.
Just a moment.
>> I want more.
>> Me, too.
>> Owner likes to joke. They say war, but
you don't have to worry about it. This
is the best for wood, which is called
Chinese ready-to-cook. Once [laughter]
again, it's not a war, it's a war of a
vegetable.
A lot of my guests have they after they
tried it, the texture of this wood is
similar to radish.
But wait till you eat it. Let me tell
you why.
>> Guys, he didn't know it was worm, okay?
It's not a worm.
Good.
It's good.
>> Really?
>> [music]
>> Baby clothes.
>> I tell you with Starbucks and the dough.
>> Everybody, we're going to try some
Korean style dumplings.
>> Yay!
>> Even the name of this vendor is called
Legendary King Dumplings. Yeah. It's
really different from Japanese or
Chinese one.
>> I'm assuming that's the kimchi one.
>> [music]
>> Hey guys, we're going to try. Let's try
the shrimp ones.
>> [music]
>> Hey, I want to try the shrimp one first.
It's not good. It's good.
>> [music]
>> Let's try the kimchi one.
>> kimchi dumpling
You're going to like the shrimp. It's
good.
>> [music]
>> This one's good and pork. Try the gyoza.
I like this.
>> So, that means that only about the raw
one. You want to try really nice quality
of Korean beef barbecue. I really
recommend to go to Madang Market. Local
style market Madang has really nice
quality beer, but
>> We're going to eat beef tartare here,
but I won't eat
I don't want to eat raw beef.
Salmon tartare is good, but beef, I
don't know. Kind of crossed the line.
Wow.
We know. Shot, shot, shot, shot, shot,
shot,
>> Let's them meet each other. Like this.
And you need to be creative there when
you could see each other. And it's
simple. Pull lever only one time. When I
pull lever, lever make air go inside of
it. Air, carbon dioxide of a beer will
meet each other. And they're going to
make a foam. Just squeeze the lever only
one time. Like this.
>> Okay, guys. This is how you make a soju.
The real one, the authentic. So, two
shot glasses, the Korean way. Two shot
glasses.
So, there. The machine tip until there.
And [laughter] then this one is a beer.
Wait, the brand
is a brand. Until here.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, now. This is the steering
something to make the foam.
It says 5% alcohol, right? Really?
Where's the beer? Guys, look at the
beer.
Let's make a foam.
Wow. Again, again, again.
Okay. Yeah, guys. I'm going to try this
one. The first time we had this, I was
with Bea also in Paris in I forgot the
one that Montmartre.
Yeah.
Yeah, somewhere there. A shop somewhere
there. Anyway, let's try it here in
Korea. I'm scared.
>> Well, it should be fresh.
>> Mhm, it's better.
>> Really?
>> Yeah, it's better.
There's like sesame flavor.
Yeah, it's flavored.
It's better.
>> Guys, meron ganto.
>> We got a lot of food at the middle.
>> Yeah, we got the
>> There are a lot of traveler who said
they
>> Pinaka masarap this shop.
>> So, say with me.
>> [music]
[music]
>> It's good.
>> Yeah.
>> Really?
It's really good.
>> [music]
>> Okay, let's learn also one drinking game
in Korea. Is it okay?
>> Yeah.
>> Just go one shot. One shot means bottoms
up.
>> Bottoms up.
>> If somebody loses the game, rest of the
people have to say one shot.
>> One shot.
>> So, everybody, all players have to take
turns and drop a little amount of soju
instead of the soju glass. Whoever makes
this soju glass into the bottom, the
person going to be a loser.
>> One shot. One shot.
>> That was a nice pour. You didn't drip
any extra.
>> Thank you.
OH, NO.
>> ONE SHOT. ONE SHOT. ONE SHOT. One shot.
>> Last food here is live octopus, guys.
Live octopus. But, I'm not going to eat
it.
>> I think I'm going to try it.
My niece is a vlogger. That's why.
>> [laughter]
>> And she's including me. I don't like it,
though.
Oh, look, Bea.
It's really moving.
This one, this one.
>> god.
>> Okay.
>> Oh my god, it's moving. What the heck?
Oh my god.
Hello, it's trying to escape. Oh, IT'S
>> [laughter]
>> SO CUTE.
>> COME ON, let's try it.
>> How is it?
>> It tastes
>> Okay, guys. This one. Is it moving?
Yeah, it is.
Okay, I'm going to try it.
>> [laughter]
>> So chewy.
I'm killing it then I'll swallow it.
>> No.
>> We're going to have dessert and and now
um twisted donuts and pinipit the talaga
sa Pilipinas guys. Ang tawag diyan is
pinipit.
>> Pinipit?
>> Pinipit and let's see if it's worth the
hype. The hell now. Pinipit now daw
siya. Pinipit ang pinipit dito. But
since we're on tour, we can get it
again. #FilipinoPride.
>> next to me.
>> [music]
[music]
>> In the Philippines, this is called
pinipit.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah. Thank you.
>> Before we can we take a photo with your
photo and next to you, is it okay? If
you sit together right next to the
>> Guys, so we're done with the tour and I
actually would recommend it because kayo
ma mabubusog agad and it's not just
eating meron ding learning and
makikilala mo din yung mga kasama mo.
And it's just so funny because nag-exit
siya ng agad-agad.
But yeah, we're going to try some food
pa. My fried chicken kaya dito. I want
to try fried chicken here. We just got
curious. Malay. Strawberry eh.
>> What is it good?
Nothing special.
Would I buy this again? No.
If I don't eat fried chicken.
>> [music]
>> You want try food on?
>> Is it good?
>> Same day we're here at Myeongdong. We're
going to try the standing Galbi, but I
don't know if it's [music] here.
>> [music]
>> It is my pillow. And then I know that it
is because my pillow. It's a low-key
place. Hello, there's a line now. I
know.
Worth it. Is it good here? Yeah, it's
very good.
>> 10 out of 10.
>> So worth it you online.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> Are you going to eat your rice?
>> Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I have a
banana
cuz it there's no cheese.
>> I can't eat some noodles without cheese.
>> Yes, I won't like talk that much cuz say
I don't want to bring out my lapel.
But I think it is my mom's facial
expression.
You know guys know me.
feeler
And I'm say this
Cuz they
feeler
Can I just share?
>> [music]
>> countries
in English
Asian better
I noticed
like you [\h__\h]
I warned you
okay
Caucasian countries
they not
See this is cool
beauty
But it
Asian
standards
Filipino
here
I shared
we're in line.
So bored
share
So you're going to
your own rice
>> [music]
>> to put water It's just like that.
I haven't tried that
>> [music]
[music]
[singing]
>> First bite.
You know what?
And it's very scrum.
Now
Try sweet rice.
>> [music]
>> We're going to eat and enjoy the and
enjoy
>> [music]
>> This is their like um
And then I was like
For the quality,
Well,
So,
We're in
Hong Dae.
>> [music]
>> Guys, it's a Monday night by the way.
It's a holiday.
>> [laughter]
>> Yes, I can only
before 1:00 a.m.
>> 5:00 a.m.
>> Do I have passport?
>> No way.
>> I have [music] passport on Monday
tomorrow.
>> [music]
>> Morning my little fatty. Welcome or
welcome back to my YouTube channel and
here's a day in my life in Korea. Yes,
[music] guys, I'm in Korea for healing.
because
I don't know. I don't know. I feel like
it's the girliest visa country. Well, I
don't know, but yeah, I'm going to get
my makeup now in morning. [music] And of
course, I have my Grace and Glow
Midnight Siren body mist. And yes, guys,
>> And I'm just going to spray [music] a
little. Guys, don't mind the color.
Room. But anyway, [music] so yeah.
So, here is the Men Deserve Body Mist.
My difference to the perfume and body
mist as in the game corporate
incorporate.
As in the game mix just a skin more so
my goodness. So, I need difference.
>> [music]
>> That that [music] is good. So, if you
want to check this out, I will leave a
link somewhere here. Okay, go. Check out
the net.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Guys, Korean up.
I can pass off as a Korean now.
>> [laughter]
>> Guys,
this is the final look and I love it.
I love it.
Guys, I'm here with my boyfriend.
>> [laughter]
>> And we are going to palace. Young book
palace. That but I'm going to wear
Hanbok. [music] But then I'm like I
don't know.
Sun book. No, no. And then after we're
going to see on soon.
Yes, of course.
And then I got to go in.
Okay, it's up to you now sign.
Sun book the
here at Young book palace.
>> [music]
[laughter]
>> music
We're in
And I wasn't able to blog
the palace cuz I just really went there
to take pictures. And I posted it
And it was so
Guys, you know what? When you're in
Europe
Sorry, huh?
Like anywhere
the
honey butter almond spread
Guys, we're hungry now.
hungry
Because it's so in it. So we're going to
be coming.
Hey, do you know what?
We're at a cafe.
Guys
Guys, you know what? I don't You know I
don't drink iced tea. allergic to my
drinks
It's so in it.
peach iced tea
I needed this.
That is so good. Wow. tea and fettuccine
pasta
Guys, while waiting for our food let me
see this.
I'm just joking.
Amen. Thank you, Lord. Thank you for
Mama Mama and thank you
Thank you.
That's our order.
Smile, Mama Mama.
Mama Mama smile.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay.
>> [music]
[laughter]
>> Guys, let's try this steak.
I'll take it.
>> [music]
>> I like this.
So, Mama Patty, I went shopping.
It's not allowed to vlog inside Chanel.
I bought another classic flap. I really,
really love this and I've been working
hard.
So, that tomorrow I
Okay. Now, you guys we're going to tax
refund. So, let's go there. Tax refund.
Look at that.
I passed by a baby clothes store.
I want to buy for Kopi.
So, I don't know if we're
So cute.
Next time na lang. Kopi, I love you.
Okay.